<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<menu>
	<menuitems sourceurl="http://spot.colorado.edu/~halloran/sqrl.html">
		<item type="squirrel">
			<species>Abert Squirrels</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[Abert squirrels (Sciurus aberti) are only found in mountain regions of North America. In the United States their range extends from extreme south-central Wyoming to New Mexico and Arizona. There are six valid subspecies including S.a. ferreus, True, the subspecies that is found along the Front Range of the Rocky Mountains in Colorado. Abert squirrels are limited to Ponderosa pine (Pinus ponderosa) forests in which they feed and build their nests.]]>
			</location>
		</item type="squirrel">
		<item type="squirrel">
			<species>Douglas Squirrels</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[Douglas squirrels (Tamiasciurus douglasii) are found throughout the coniferous forests of Southwestern British Columbia, western Washington, western Oregon, and western California.]]>
			</location>
		</item>
		<item type="squirrel">
			<species>Eastern Grey Squirrels</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[Eastern gray squirrels are found throughout the eastern United States; their natural range extends from Florida, north to Canada, and west to where the deciduous forests meet the great plains grasslands. There are 5 subspecies of eastern grey squirrels, S. carolinensis carolinensis is the subspecies found in most of the south from northern Florida, to North Carolina, west to Missouri, and eastern Texas.]]>
			</location>
		</item>
		<item type="squirrel">
			<species>Fox Squirrels</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[Fox squirrels are found throughout the eastern United States; their natural range extends from Florida, north to Canada, and west to the Dakotas, Colorado, and Texas, but they are not found in New England. ]]>
			</location>
		</item>
		<item type="squirrel">
			<species>Northern Flying Squirrels</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[Northern Flying Squirrels (Glaucomys sabrinus) are found throughout coniferous and hardwood forests of Eastern Alaska and the southern tier of Canada. In the United States they extend from the Canadian Border south though California, Idaho, Montana, the Great Lakes Region south through the Appalachians. ]]>
			</location>
		</item>
		<item type="squirrel">
			<species>Pine Squirrels</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[Pine squirrels (Tamiasciurus hudsonicus) are found throughout much of Canada and Alaska. In the Continental United States. Their range extends through the Rocky Mountains and the Northeast south to Virginia.]]>
			</location>
		</item>
		<item type="squirrel">
			<species>Southern Flying Squirrels</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[Southern Flying Squirrels (Glaucomys volans) are found throughout the Eastern United States west to Minnesota, Kansas and Texas, however they are absent from New England and the tip of Florida. They favor hardwood forests such as oak-hickory, beech-maple, and live oak.]]>
			</location>
		</item>
		<item type="squirrel">
			<species>Western Grey Squirrels</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[Western Grey Squirrels (Sciurus griseus) are also known as California Grey Squirrels, and are the only large grey tree squirrel in their range on the Western Coast of the United States. Western Grey Squirrels are found in the Pacific States from Washington to California.]]>
			</location>
		</item>
		<item type="monkey">
			<species>Unknown</species>
			<location>
				<![CDATA[If I told you, I'd have to kill you.  Not that it matters since this item should not appear in the list.]]>
			</location>
		</item>
	</menuitems>
</menu>